[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie, produced by Judd Apatow, was written by two of its actors - Seth Rogen and Evan Goldberg when they were 13 years old.", "correct_answer": "Superbad", "incorrect_answers": ["Kicking and Screaming", "Fun with Dick and Jane", "Knocked Up"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the natural habitat of the bacteria?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["The air and sea water", "Earths surface and fresh water", "Underground and the icebergs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The standing long jump and the standing high jump were once Olympic sports.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Several scenes were cut from this drama directed by Adrian Lyne because the studio deemed them psychologically damaging.", "correct_answer": "9\u00bd Weeks", "incorrect_answers": ["Blue Velvet", "Platoon", "Sid and Nancy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the largest mall in the North American continent.", "correct_answer": "The West Edmonston Mall", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mall at 4", "The  Bergen Mall", "The Center"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1982 movie The Thing is set at the North Pole.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This food was not on the Sopranos, but is a Taiwanese dish.", "correct_answer": "Bao Bing", "incorrect_answers": ["FuFu", "Cibreo", "Ngapi-jaw"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of Dr. Seusss famous characters said Save the Trees !!! Let em Grow ! ?", "correct_answer": "the Lorax", "incorrect_answers": ["Horton", "Sam-I-Am", "the Cat in the Hat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1986 sci-fi film directed by David Cronenberg is a remake of a 1958 film?", "correct_answer": "The Fly", "incorrect_answers": ["Braindead", "The Thing", "Scanners"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What impressive physical characteristic did Charles Darwin possess, which made the Bank of England use his image for the ten pound note in 2000?", "correct_answer": "Large beard", "incorrect_answers": ["Distinctive eyes", "Very big ears", "Unique nose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a gadwall?", "correct_answer": "A duck", "incorrect_answers": ["A submarine", "A cannon", "A firewall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Superbad, Seth gets spit on by a guy named Jesse who tells him that he is not invited to his party.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]